<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marty &amp; Domi</title>
    <link>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Marty &amp; Domi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/about-us/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; Who are you? Our friends, family, and simply people with whom we want to spend time. We as a group share an interest in the world, humor, and the desire to have fun. Around you will be a lot of other great people with interesting topics and stories to tell.&#xA;Who are we? 👩‍❤️‍👨 Hello! We are a lad and a girl who decided that they want to be together, forever&amp;hellip; or at least until the first big fight 😅.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/contact/</guid>
      <description> &amp;nbsp; Contacts Groom and Bride Marťas +420 607 558 487 holoubekm / @ / gmail.com Domi +420 724 875 203 dominika.hubova / @ / gmail.com Witnesses Vojta +420 XXX XXX XXX holoubekv / @ / gmail.com Paulinka +420 XXX XXX XXX &amp;nbsp; </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; What, who, a wedding?! It&amp;rsquo;s true&amp;hellip; Dominika was not scared enough and said yes.&#xA;We really appreciate that you want to spend our special day with us. Therefore, we crafted this website to make it easier for everyone.&#xA;We are looking forward to seeing you on August 17, 2024 at Jitkovský Mlýn, a short distance from Chotěboř&#xA;And what will you find out on the pages for example?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://martas-a-domi.cz/en/info/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp; Location The wedding will take place at the former agricultural farm and mill, located near the small village of Jitkov. The premises include an old barn, a vast courtyard, a guest-house with apartments and facilities for guests and visitors, a pond, and the surrounding meadows. All of this is nestled within the beautiful scenery of the Vysočina region.&#xA;Transport By car: Pension Jitkovský Mlýn, 583 01 Jitkov, Chotěboř By train: Havlíčkův Brod (approx.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
